# Tyler Russell Missouri State University - Student

629 S Fairway Ave, Springfield, MO
(314) 578 6985
Tyler.wayne2002@hotmail.com
linkedin.com/in/tyler-russell251

SUMMARY
Student with an in-progress degree in <b>Computer Science and Mathematics</b> . Experienced with customer service via restaurant employers. Proficient in Microsoft Office utilities, along with several programs regarding code development such as Microsoft Virtual Studio Code. Self-taught in developmental programs such as popular Adobe programs, Unity game engine, and Blender modelling.
EXPERIENCE

#### PODCAST EDITOR - Eureka, MO

Freelance, 2018 - 2019

- Utilized audio programs to create an enjoyable listening experience.
- Networked through peers to find new clients.

#### LION'S CHOICE - Eureka, MO

Team Member, 2019 - 2020

- Managed inventory and stocked items according to company standards.
- Prepared food in a high traffic setting while maintaining expert-level customer service.
- Conducted orders via a tablet and training my co-workers to do so.

#### **ORANGE LEAF - Springfield, MO**

Key Carrier (Shift Leader), September 2021 - Present

- Managed inventory and stocked items according to company standards.
- Supervised and trained new employees.
- Administered the opening and closing of the restaurant.
- Resolved all customer conflicts and questions without the assistance of my employer.
- Prepared the entire range of the restaurant's menu.

## EDUCATION ..... ADDITIONAL SKILLS .....

### MISSOURI STATE UNIVERSITY - Springfield, MO

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, May 2024
Degree in-progress

#### • Proficient in Adobe Programs and Unity Engine.

- Currently working on a long-term personal project with the Unity Engine in C#.
- History of musical awards and achievements in Collegiate Jazz.